export default data = [
  {
      question: "Follow the ______ closely, and you will find it easy to assemble the bicycle",
      options: ["functions","diagnoses","appointments","instructions"],
      correct_option: "instructions"
  },
  {
      question: "If I can help you with the project, don’t ______ to call me",
      options: ["concern","hesitate","notify","submit"],
      correct_option: "hesitate"
  },
  {
      question: "______ between good friends should be resolved, not ignored",
      options: ["ompliments","oncerns","onflicts","onnections"],
      correct_option: "onflicts"
  },
  {
      question: "Group registrations are not allowed.  Each member must register for the conference ______",
      options: ["comfortably","individually","intelligently","respectfully"],
      correct_option: "individually"
  },
  {
      question: "Mr. Wang’s arguments were very ______ , and the committee finally accepted his proposal",
      options: ["artificial","inappropriate","persuasive","descriptive"],
      correct_option: "persuasive"
  },
  {
      question: "The woman is so ______ that she cries every time she hears a sad story",
      options: ["casual","harsh","intimate","sentimental"],
      correct_option: "sentimental"
  },
  {
      question: "We ______ believe that with your intelligence and hard work, you will pass the exam without any difficulty",
      options: ["firmly","extremely","strictly","inquiringly"],
      correct_option: "firmly"
  },
  {
      question: "If we walk at this slow ______ , we’ll never get to our destination on time",
      options: ["mood","pace","tide","access"],
      correct_option: "pace"
  },
  {
      question: "The territorial dispute can be ______ back to the year 1917, when the two countries were at war",
      options: ["held","recalled","traced","switched"],
      correct_option: "traced"
  },
  {
      question: "One key factor to success is to have a definite goal first and then do your best to ______ the goal",
      options: ["attain","contest","encounter","struggle"],
      correct_option: "attain"
  },
  {
      question: "Jane and Sue are twins, but they seem to have nothing ______",
      options: ["in common","in comparison","in contact","in contrast"],
      correct_option: "in common"
  },
  {
      question: "How did the traffic accident ______ ?",
      options: ["come about","come around","come off","come over"],
      correct_option: "come about"
  },
  {
      question: "During the lunch hour, Jane ______ her notes so she would remember them for the test",
      options: ["ran into","ran off","ran out of","ran over"],
      correct_option: "ran over"
  },
  {
      question: "We shall expect you at eight o’clock; ______ , it’s an informal dinner",
      options: ["by accident","by all means","by the way","by then"],
      correct_option: "by the way"
  },
  {
      question: "Stricter measures have been taken to ______ potential dangers concerning cigarette-smoking",
      options: ["ward off","give in","check out","hang up"],
      correct_option: "ward off"
  },
]
